<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Tokens version="1.0">
	<File path="Protocols/RKMappingOperationDataSource.html">
		
		<Token>
			<TokenIdentifier>//apple_ref/occ/intf/RKMappingOperationDataSource</TokenIdentifier>
			<Abstract type="html">An object that adopts the RKMappingOperationDataSource protocol is responsible for the retrieval or creation of target objects within an RKMapperOperation or RKMappingOperation. A data source is responsible for meeting the requirements of the underlying data store implementation and must return a key-value coding compliant object instance that can be used as the target object of a mapping operation. It is also responsible for commiting any changes necessary to the underlying data store once a mapping operation has completed its work.</Abstract>
			<DeclaredIn>RKMappingOperationDataSource.h</DeclaredIn>
			
			<NodeRef refid="63"/>
		</Token>
		
		
		<Token>
			<TokenIdentifier>//apple_ref/occ/intfm/RKMappingOperationDataSource/mappingOperation:targetObjectForRepresentation:withMapping:</TokenIdentifier>
			<Abstract type="html">Asks the data source for the target object for an object mapping operation given an NSDictionary representation of the object&apos;s properties and the mapping object that will be used to perform the mapping.</Abstract>
			<DeclaredIn>RKMappingOperationDataSource.h</DeclaredIn>			
			
			<Declaration>- (id)mappingOperation:(RKMappingOperation *)mappingOperation targetObjectForRepresentation:(NSDictionary *)representation withMapping:(RKObjectMapping *)mapping</Declaration>
			<Parameters>
				<Parameter>
					<Name>mappingOperation</Name>
					<Abstract type="html">The mapping operation requesting the target object.</Abstract>
				</Parameter><Parameter>
					<Name>representation</Name>
					<Abstract type="html">A dictionary representation of the properties to be mapped onto the retrieved target object.</Abstract>
				</Parameter><Parameter>
					<Name>mapping</Name>
					<Abstract type="html">The object mapping to be used to perform a mapping from the representation to the target object.</Abstract>
				</Parameter>
			</Parameters>
			<ReturnValue><Abstract type="html">A key-value coding compliant object to perform the mapping on to.</Abstract></ReturnValue>
			<Anchor>//api/name/mappingOperation:targetObjectForRepresentation:withMapping:</Anchor>
		</Token>
		
		<Token>
			<TokenIdentifier>//apple_ref/occ/intfm/RKMappingOperationDataSource/commitChangesForMappingOperation:error:</TokenIdentifier>
			<Abstract type="html">Tells the data source to commit any changes to the underlying data store.</Abstract>
			<DeclaredIn>RKMappingOperationDataSource.h</DeclaredIn>			
			
			<Declaration>- (BOOL)commitChangesForMappingOperation:(RKMappingOperation *)mappingOperation error:(NSError **)error</Declaration>
			<Parameters>
				<Parameter>
					<Name>mappingOperation</Name>
					<Abstract type="html">The mapping operation that has completed its work.</Abstract>
				</Parameter><Parameter>
					<Name>error</Name>
					<Abstract type="html">A pointer to an error to be set in the event that the mapping operation could not be committed.</Abstract>
				</Parameter>
			</Parameters>
			<ReturnValue><Abstract type="html">A Boolean value indicating if the changes for the mapping operation were committed successfully.</Abstract></ReturnValue>
			<Anchor>//api/name/commitChangesForMappingOperation:error:</Anchor>
		</Token>
		
	</File>
</Tokens>